the mechanism whereby I
imagined it would happen
is that we would
make models that were
good at coding and
good at AI research
and we would use
that to produce the
next generation of model
and speed it up
to create a loop
that would increase the
speed of model development
We are now in
terms of the models
that write code I
have engineers within Anthropa
who say don't write
any code anymore I
just let the model
write the I edit
it I do the
around it I think
I don't know we
might be 6 to
12 months away from
when the is doing
most all of what
do end to end
And then it's a
of how fast does
that loop close Not
every part of that
is something that can
be sped up by
AI right There's like
There's manufacture of There's
training time for the
it's you I think
there's a lot of
It's easy to see
how this could take
a years I don't
it's very hard for
me to see how
it could take longer
than that But if
I had to I
would guess that this
goes faster than people
imagine And that key
element of code and
increasingly research going faster
than we imagine that's
going to be the
key driver